{
    "subject": "resource/Arizona_Summit_Law_School",
    "predicate": "ontology/facultySize",
    "object": "38",
    "human_readable": "The faculty size of Arizona Summit Law School is 38.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9475805163383484,
            "question": "What is the faculty size at Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9412441849708557,
            "question": "What is the approximate size of the faculty at Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9016396999359131,
            "question": "Arizona Summit Law School has a faculty size of... ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8973874449729919,
            "question": "Is the faculty size of Arizona Summit Law School large or small?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896675109863281,
            "question": "What does the number '38' represent in relation to Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8884912133216858,
            "question": "Could you give me a number representing the faculty size of Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7867379784584045,
            "question": "How many faculty members are there at Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116759419441223,
            "question": "Give me a numerical value for the number of instructors at Arizona Summit Law School."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6736789345741272,
            "question": "How many teachers are there at Arizona Summit Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6575765609741211,
            "question": "If Arizona Summit Law School had twice the number of faculty members, how many would there be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The faculty size of Arizona Summit Law School is 38.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4745_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many teachers are there at Arizona Summit Law School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4745_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give me a numerical value for the number of instructors at Arizona Summit Law School.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4745_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many faculty members are there at Arizona Summit Law School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4745_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4745_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text excerpts do not mention the faculty size of Arizona Summit Law School.  Therefore, we cannot confirm if it's 38. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe context information provided indicates that the average salary at Arizona Summit Law School is $93,497 per year. This implies that employees at Arizona Summit Law School get a higher salary compared to other companies in the same industry or category (Higher Education). The comparison with other similar educational institutions, such as Special Focus Institutions, also suggests that salaries are higher at Arizona Summit Law School. Therefore, the information supports the statement that Arizona Summit Law School employees get a higher salary than other similar companies."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about the specific faculty size at Arizona Summit Law School, hence the response is \"no\" as there is no supporting evidence for the statement that the faculty size is 38."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of the faculty size being 38 anywhere in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}